

AMAN TIWARI

UI/UX DESIGNER



+919529500975



tiwariaman0305@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/aman-tiwari-9a2267218/

Education

B. Tech Computer Engineering Guru Gobind Singh College Of Engineering 2020-2024 Nashik Maharashtra

Higher Secondary School

Sandip Global School and Junior College

2018-2020 Nashik Maharashtra

Certifications

- Graphic Design with Photoshop (Great learning)
- Basics of UI/UX Foundation (great learning)
- AWS Academy Data Analytics (AWS Academy)
- · AWS Academy Cloud Foundation(AWS Academy)

Interests

Atheletic Player (University level) - 100 meter

Football

Cricket

Kabbaddi (District Level)

Language

English HIndi

Marathi

About me

I am a passionate and creative UI/UX designer with a keen eye for detail and a love for creating intuitive and engaging use interfaces. I recently graduated with a degree in BE In Computer Engineering, and I have hands-on experience in UI/UX design.

Experience

JR.UI/Ux Designer

Aug 2024-Present

EagleByte Solutions Pvt.Ltd

Creative and detail-oriented UI/UX Designer with a passion for crafting intuitive and user-centric digital experiences. Committed to continuous learning and staying updated with the latest design trends to create impactful and accessible interface

Graphic Designer

Oct 2023-2024

Intern Savy

Contributed to client interactions, incorporating feedback to deliver creative solutions, and actively participated in professional development opportunities to enhance designskills.

Community Manager Intern

Oct 2023-Nov 2023

Fostered online community engagement through social media platforms, responding to inquiries, moderating discussions, and creating content that enhanced brand presence.

Software Developer Intern

Jan 2023-Mar 2023

P. S. Technologies

Developed a solid understanding of web application development technologies, including Java Server Pages (JSP) and Java-based backend frameworks (Model View-Controller (MVC) architectural pattern).

Skills

Adobe photoshop

Canva

Figma, wireframing, prototype

MS Office

HTML

css